Use these tips when taking inventory: 1. Fight for a bag with your teammates, but what should you do if there is no space in the bag?
Just quickly drag out the gun and backpack strap and throw it on the ground before your teammates react.
Take it slowly. 2. If you think some equipment is too expensive, you can go to Jinxi District to exchange it.
For example, this best Wutou sells for RMB 430,000 for one flight, but the exchange rate in Jinxi District only costs RMB 6,790,000.
Very good deal. 3. In the design, the acrylic and left and right tilt heads are designed as the same buttons.
The probe can be automatically acrylic. Compared with the same period, we designed acrylic and fire as the same button.
It can hold its breath when seeing people. The only flaw is that it cannot push the gun. Ah, damn you! Four,
Bu Chongxi was diving but jumped to the floor. He might accidentally fall into the water. In fact, we only need to walk close to the side,
It's 100% guaranteed to fall into the water. Five, many people on the bus will come to eat the medical pile in this turtle car.
We lie down here, and then climb up, and we can hide behind this medical pile. If someone comes, just steal it.
Very easy to use. There is just a small problem. Bu Chongxi can't find any way to get out of here.
Sixth, the Veyron was very loud when it turned on and was running away. The Veyron was headhunted as soon as its position was exposed.
The sound of the tiger lantern is much quieter, so we can just turn on the tiger lantern and drive on the road. Why are you so selfish? seven,
The ballistics of the first few rounds of M-4 are very serious, so we shoot the first few rounds when we turn on the machine.
This will make you much more stable when facing the gun later. Have you learned these tips on how to use Huff Coin in gun battles?
If you know how to call your brother, let him shine. Old guy.